http://www.eyeonstarwars.com/privacy.html

The only site your need to know for Star Wars Episode I, II, III, & the original trilogy.
Privacy Policy
EyeonStarWars.com respects your privacy.
Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of EyeonStarWars.com.
Credit card details
EyeonStarWars.com will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on EyeonStarWars.com.
External Sites
EyeonStarWars.com is not responsible for the content of external internet sites, including our advertisers. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.
Cookies
A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows EyeonStarWars.com to recognize you each time you visit this site. Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and EyeonStarWars.com does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.
Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet
While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to EyeonStarWars.com and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through EyeonStarWars.com have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.
Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.
| Art of Coruscant ]
View this site's Privacy Policy.
Contact the Webmaster.
STAR WARS(R), THE EMPIRE STRIKES BACK (R), RETURN OF THE JEDI (TM)
and THX(R) and associated elements and logos are property of Lucasfilm Ltd.
All content in The Star Wars Network (e.g., clips, stills, designs, artwork,
etc.) is copyright of their respected owners.
Images of the Star Wars
movies are protected by intellectual property laws of and any use other
than for private, non-commercial purposes is strictly prohibited.
All site content is ©Copyright 2001 EyeonStarWars.com.
All rights reserved.
Reproduction in whole or in part without permission is prohibited.
Site maintained and hosted by SBA Design.
